const dayThreeQuestions = [
  {
    question: "How many times does a Muslim offer obligatory prayers in a day?",
    options: ["Three times", "Four times", "Five times", "Six times"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Surah (chapter) of the Quran is recited in every rakath of salah (prayers)?",
    options: [
      "Al-Ikhlas (chapter 112)",
      "An-Nas (chapter 114)",
      "Al-Fatihah (chapter 1)",
      "Al-Ala (chapter 87)",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which direction do Muslims face while offering salah (prayers)?",
    options: [
      "Kabah (Makkah)",
      "Baitul Muqaddas (Al-Aqsa Mosque Palestine)",
      "Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque (Dubai)",
      "The Al-Fateh Mosque (Bahrain)",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which prayer does Allah mention in the Holy Quran as His most-favoured prayer?",
    options: [
      "Fajr Salah (pre-dawn prayers)",
      "Asar Salah (middle prayers)",
      "Zuhr Salah (mid-afternoon prayers)",
      "Maghrib prayers (sunset prayers)",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "How do Muslims begin their prayers?",
    options: [
      "By Saying Bismillah (In the Name of Allah)",
      "By Saying Subhanallah (Glory be to Allah)",
      "By Saying Alhamdulillah (All praise is due to Allah)",
      "By Saying Allahu Akbar (By pronouncing the greatness of Almighty Allah)",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many rakath (units of prayers) does a Muslim pray during the obligatory maghrib salah (prayers)?",
    options: ["Two rakath", "Three rakath", "Four rakath", "None of the above"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among Muslims have the privilege to stand in the first row for salah (prayers), behind the Imam?",
    options: [
      "Powerful men have the right to stand in the front row during salah (prayers)",
      "Men from Saudi Arabia have the right to stand in the front row during salah (prayers)",
      "White men have the right to stand in the front row during salah (prayers)",
      "There is no privilege to anyone to stand in the first row. Even a king stands in the row besides an ordinary man during salah (prayers)",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Are women allowed to go to mosques to offer prayers?",
    options: [
      "No, women are not allowed in the mosque",
      "Women can only listen to prayers",
      "Yes, women can offer prayers in mosques, provided there are separate facilities and provision",
      "Women can pray in the mosque, standing right beside the men",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What should Muslims perform before offering salah (prayers)?",
    options: [
      "Wearing of skull-cap",
      "Wearing of perfume",
      "Wudu (ablution)",
      "Clipping of nails",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the call for prayer called?",
    options: ["Adhan", "Takbeer", "Kalimah", "Salah"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
];
export default dayThreeQuestions;
